{
    "quizQuestion":[
        {
            "question":"What is the default behaviour of React when rendering a list",
            "options":["Keys", "Refs", "State", "Props"],
            "correctAnswer": 0,
            "points": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "Which keyword is used to define a constant in React?",
            "options" : ["let", "var", "const", "def"],
            "correctAnswer": 2,
            "points": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "Which method is used to render React elements in the DOM?",
            "options" :["render", "hydrate", "setState", "call"],
            "correctAnswer": 0,
            "points":10
        },
        {
            "question": "What is React primarly used for?",
            "options": ["Database", "Frontend", "Backend", "Server"],
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question":"What property holds the data in a React Component",
            "options": ["props", "state", "keys", "context"],
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "points": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "Which React hook is used for side effects?",
            "options": ["useState", "useEffect", "useContext", "useRef"],
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "What is passed to components to make them dynamic",
            "options": ["Keys", "Refs", "State", "Props"],
            "correctAnswer": 3,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which keyword is used to export a component?",
            "options": ["export", "import", "Require", "Module"],
            "correctAnswer": 0,
            "points": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the default port for React development server?",
            "options": ["3000", "8000", "4000", "2000"],
            "correctAnswer":0,
            "points": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "Which allows you to manage state in functional components?",
            "options":["useEffect", "useContext", "useState", "useMemo"],
            "correctAnswer":1,
            "points":5
        }
    ]
}